The Amanda Steele Show, today's goes to incompetency.
The big fancy jewelry brand, Van Cleef & Our Pals,
accidentally sent $150,000 to the wrong account.
So now they're suing to get their money back,
but they don't even know who they're suing.
It's just like a general sue.
Despite all their efforts to sort it out,
they're hitting a dead end, so they're taking legal action,
hoping to track down whoever's got their cash.
But I hope it went to a Black person,
because it's like, you know what?
Reparations today, reparations tomorrow, reparations forever.
Today's letdown goes to the carbon family being inside of Lunchables.
Consumer Reports have recently said that Lunchables
have concerning levels of lead and sodium.
Not lead.
Lead.
We gonna need to sign a waiver just to set foot in a grocery store sometime soon.
I went on a toxic tour where we went all over the nation to different cities
and learned all about the ways in which environmental racism is taking place.
Majority of the housing projects that were built in the 70s, lead-based paint.
But lead-based paint affects your brain function.
It affects the development of your frontal lobe.
It affects the ability to have rational responses to things.
When they talk about like, oh, like the hood is so dangerous,
a lot of that can also be attributed to the fact that
the environment that people are literally living in
is affecting their cognitive ability to have conflict resolution.
We are, we are, we are.